英文字幕:
官方
翻译: 谷歌翻译
润色，压制:
Bolshevik0
Hi everybody. My name is Kirill Yudintsev. I'm the creative director at Gaijin
大家好 我叫Kirill Yudintsev 我是Gaijin的创意总监
and right now I'd like to tell you a little about the latest update 1.77, Advancing Storm.
现在我想告诉你一些关于1.77前行暴风这个最新更新的消息
We've had a lot of feedback about the latest update. Thanks for writing to us.
我们收到了很多最新的更新的反馈 感谢您写信给我们
Your feedback is very important and useful to us.
你们的反馈对我们非常重要和有用的
Among other things, a lot of the feedback was about the new engine, the new renderer, the new graphics, and the changes to the game's performance
除此之外 很多反馈都是关于新引擎 新渲染器 新图形以及游戏性能的变化
Performance has improved for some players and become worse for others.
一些玩家的游戏性能表现有所改善 而其他玩家的则变得更糟
Some of the players who experienced worse performance were using supersampling (SSAA x4).
有些声称自己游戏性能变差的玩家 正在使用超级采样（SSAA x4）
Supersampling is the most resource-intensive form of anti-aliasing.
超采样是最耗费资源的反锯齿形式
We don't recommend enabling it unless your video card is very powerful and you get at least 200 FPS without it.
我们不建议启用它 除非你的显卡功能非常强大 譬如说在没开抗锯齿的时候能达到200FPS
For everyone else there are options that are simpler in terms of performance and can provide results that are just as good
对于其他人来说 在性能方面有更简单的选项 并且可以提供同样优秀的结果
HQ TAA, just TAA, or even HQ FXAA.
使用HQ TAA 只是TAA 甚至是HQ FXAA
These are perfectly decent types of anti-aliasing that provide very nice image quality.
这些都是非常不错的抗锯齿类型 可以提供非常好的图像质量
The new engine has given the game a lot of new capabilities, but we've still got some things to work on
新引擎赋予游戏很多新功能 但我们仍然有一些工作要做
and there's definitely room to improve optimization
并且有改善优化的空间
these new capabilities require a lot of configuration and we need to take a lot of nuances into account.
这些新功能需要大量配置 我们需要考虑很多细微差别
The update just came out, and at some point over the next six months
这个更新刚刚出来 并在接下来的六个月的某个时候
we're going to improve various aspects of the game's appearance, as well as its performance.
我们将改进游戏外观的各个方面以及其性能
So if your performance has gotten worse, it's possible that we'll be able to find a way to improve it in the future.
所以如果你的游戏性能变得更糟 也许我们以后能找到某种方法来改善
A large number of players have been asking about the navy, how the pre-cbt of the War Thunder navy has been going
许多玩家一直在问关于海战的情况 以及战雷海战的内测的内测(先行封闭beta测试)进展情况
what its eventual fate will be, and what our future plans are.
它的最终命运将是什么 以及我们未来的计划是什么
Testing is going well. We've done a lot, and we don't have all that much left on our to-do list, in general.
测试进展顺利 我们做了很多事情 总的来说 我们的待办事项清单并不是很多
we're approaching getting in to closed beta testing.
我们很快就要进行内测(封闭beta测试)
The naval has changed profoundly over the last two years.
过去两年来 海战发生了深刻的变化
It has traveled a long road from what it was at the beginning of CBT and what it has become now.
从内测开始到现在变化很大
And it's all happened exclusively thanks to our players, their feedback, and their opinions.
这些改变特别要感谢我们的玩家 以及他们的反馈和意见
We've been listening to them, we've watched them play, and we've tested and played with them.
我们一直在听他们的意见 看他们玩 自己测试或者和玩家一起玩
Our goal is to make everything fun and engaging, and we don't want naval play to disappoint our players.
我们的目标是让每件事都变得有趣和吸引人 而且我们不希望海战让我们的玩家失望
We want it to satisfy their expectations.
我们希望它能够满足玩家的期待
As far as we're concerned, we've achieved almost everything we could
就我们而言 我们已经完成了几乎所有我们可以做到的事情
everything we wanted, and everything our players wanted.
我们想要的一切 以及我们玩家想要的一切
In other words, we're at the end of this initial stage.
换句话说 我们正处于这个初始阶段的末尾
Our players often ask what our future plans are for aircraft.
我们的玩家经常会问我们未来的飞机计划是什么
They want to know why we keep coming out with all sorts of things, including modern vehicles, for tank commanders,
他们想知道为什么我们老是为坦克玩家提供各种各样的东西 包括现代坦克
but when it comes to aircraft there's nothing like that.
然而飞机这边都是不存在的
The first thing I should point out is that before we introduced ground vehicles
我应该首先指出的是 在我们引入地面载具之前
we dedicated about four years exclusively to developing the aviation.
我们专注于开发空战四年
Another four years have passed since we introduced ground vehicles,
自从我们引入地面载具后又过了四年
and during that time we've never stopped developing both parts of the game in parallel.
在那段时间里 我们从未停止过同时开发游戏的两部分
It's just that the majority of the most important things we could have implemented for aircraft have already been implemented.
只是我们可以为飞机实现的大多数最重要的事情已经实施了
We've been adding some rather significant things every year, for example,
譬如 我们每年都会增加一些相当重要的东西
we introduced gunner cockpits relatively recently,
我们最近发布的炮手视角
and we made it possible for planes to be destroyed by midair collisions with falling bombs in the same update.
而且在同一次更新中让飞机可以因空投与炸弹的碰撞而被摧毁
In general, we've been introducing all sorts of things, but they're mostly smaller things because all the big stuff has already been done.
总的来说 我们一直在更新各种各样的东西 因为所有的大功能已经完成 现在更新的都是小功能
The next major step we can take when it comes to aircraft will probably be noticed by everyone
下一个空战中的主要更新很可能引人注目
I'm talking about switching to more modern supersonic planes and introducing guided missiles and other modern aviation technology.
我指的是更现代的超音速飞机 导弹和其他现代航空技术
As I said earlier, we've been conducting and are continuing to conduct internal testing,
正如我刚才所说 我们一直在持续进行内部测试
and the results aren't exactly unambiguous.
并不是没有目标
Vehicles on this level make things complicated thanks to missiles, detection systems, and supersonic speeds.
由于导弹 探测系统和超音速 这个程度的载具让游戏机制变得更复杂
All of our players who fly planes know that jet planes are already significantly different from piston-engine planes in terms of gameplay,
所有空战玩家都知道 喷气式飞机已经与活塞式飞机的玩法有显着不同
and there are plenty of people who don't like this difference.
有很多人不喜欢这种差异
Future changes will alter the game even more, so we're working, we're testing,
未来的变化更会改变游戏 所以我们正在努力和测试
and right now I'm not ready to say that more modern aircraft will definitely appear in the game.
而现在我还没准备好说更多的现代飞机肯定会出现在游戏中
But there's still a good chance that more modern planes of some kind will be introduced.
但仍有很多机会推出某种类型的更为现代化的飞机
I can't give you any details, we're still in the research and experimentation phase
我无法给你任何细节 我们仍处于研究和实验阶段
with the goal of determining the "upper limit."
目标是确定“上限”
There's also the issue that there are fewer and fewer different production models of vehicles,
还有一个问题是 不同生产模式的载具变得越来越少
so balancing various nations becomes problematic.
所以平衡各个国家成为问题
There are a lot of nuances and questions, and this is an extremely complex task in terms of gameplay
游戏中有很多细微差别和问题 这是一个非常复杂的任务
balance, and how to explain it all to our players.
平衡 以及如何向玩家解释这一切
吐槽:
不改变已有载具数据???喵喵喵?
As you know, we don't invent new vehicles or change the stats of existing ones,
如你所知 我们不发明载具或者不改变已有载具的数据
so if balance was an issue in real life, then it's also going to be a problem with the vehicles in the game.
正如生活需要平衡 游戏载具也需要平衡
In general, there's a lot of work, and most of our players won't necessarily be pleased with the results.
一般来说 有很多工作 我们的大多数玩家不一定会对结果感到满意
That being said, in our game you don't need to play with every vehicle
这就是说 在我们的游戏中 你不需要玩每个载具
if there's something you don't like, don't play with it!
遇到了不喜欢的载具就不要玩
so we're still working on this for players who will like it, but I can't tell you more about certain plans right now.
所以我们仍然在为喜欢它的玩家做这件事 但我现在仍无可奉告
In addition, we're also experimenting with helicopters, both attack helicopters and others
另外 我们也在试验直升机 既有攻击直升机也有其他的
and here things are looking much more positive and unambiguous.
这件事推进得更快
This kind of gameplay will generally be simpler and more understandable for players.
对于玩家来说 这种游戏玩法通常会更简单和容易理解
Although helicopters are harder to fly than planes, they're also slower and have less firepower
尽管直升机比飞机更难飞 但它们也更慢 火力也更小
Shorter firing distances, and the pilot's influence in terms of piloting and shooting is greater.
射击距离更短 飞行员在驾驶和射击方面的影响力更大
So it's entirely possible that helicopters will appear in our game before modern planes do.
所以在现代飞机出现之前 直升机完全有可能出现在我们的游戏中
They also fit better with ground vehicles in terms of destroying each other, everybody loves killing tankers, right?
他们也更适合用于陆战模式 每个人都喜欢舔地 对吧
Update 1.77 Advancing Storm added new top-level ground vehicles to the game
更新1.77前行暴风增加了新的顶级地面车辆的游戏
such as the Abrams, the T-64B, and others.
如艾布拉姆斯 T-64B等
And needless to say, this has affected the balance and changed the game at high ranks and battle ratings.
不用说 这已经影响了平衡 并改变了游戏的高级别和战斗等级
In general, right now (filmed 5 days after release) we're satisfied with how they've been received by players
一般来说 现在（时间点是发布后的5天内）我们对他们被玩家的接受程度感到满意
and how they've impacted the game's balance.
以及他们如何影响游戏的平衡
But introducing top-level vehicles is bound to change the balance of all previous vehicles and will always change the game.
但是引进顶级车辆势必会改变以前所有车辆的平衡 并且会一直改变游戏规则
In other words, it's a whole new adventure.
换句话说 这是一个全新的冒险
We're therefore going to have to take another look at all of the battle ratings affected by this change, so our work here has just begun.
因此 我们将不得不重新审视受这一变化影响的所有战斗权重 所以我们的工作才刚刚开始
Write to us and tell us what you think.
写邮件给我们 告诉我们你的想法
Leave feedback in the forum or the comments, because your feedback is as important as statistics
在论坛或评论中留下反馈 因为你的反馈与统计数据一样重要
They're the two primary part of the information we work with.
它们是我们所使用信息的两个主要部分
However, while statistics show us dry facts, it doesn't do a great job of telling us how changes have been received by players
然而 虽然统计数据显示我们有些枯燥的事实 但它并没有很好地告诉我们玩家如何接受改变
or how they're affected the way the game feels to them.
或者他们如何影响游戏对他们的感受
In order to get this information we need to watch our players play.
为了获得这些信息 我们需要观看我们的玩家进行比赛
We need you to leave us feedback so we can read it.
我们需要您留下反馈意见 以便我们阅读
So write to us, we always study your feedback carefully.
所以写信给我们 我们总是仔细研究您的反馈
There will definitely be changes, both to things that are already in the game and things that are yet to come.
游戏中已有的东西和未来的东西肯定会发生变化
It always happens. But right now... right now players have been pretty positive about everything.
它总是发生 但现在 现在玩家们对所有事情都非常积极
I hope you liked update 1.77 Advancing Storm.
我希望你喜欢更新1.77前行暴风
We spent over six months working on it, almost a year
我们花了六个月的时间研究它 差不多一年
and we put a lot of effort into it.
我们付出了很多努力
Send us your feedback, write comments, "like" us, and subscribe to our channel!
向我们发送您的反馈 写下评论 “喜欢”我们 并订阅我们的频道！